<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ESC1 on Abraxas</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/esc1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ESC1 on Abraxas</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 05:28:27 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/esc1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HTB Coder</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/htb-coder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 05:28:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/htb-coder/</guid>
      <description>Coder is an Insane Windows box. I start by decompiling a C# executable used for encryption. Leveraging a deprecated encryption algorithm, I successfully decrypt an encrypted archive containing a KeePass database and key. With the key, I can access the database, revealing credentials for a TeamCity instance and a 2FA backup code. After brute-forcing the 2FA code, I gain access to TeamCity, allowing me to upload a diff to execute commands in a CI/CD pipeline. Escalating to Super User, I find past builds and uncover two new files. Using command execution from the pipeline, I identify a diff containing encrypted PowerShell credentials. Decrypting these credentials grants access to the account of E.Black, who is part of the PKI Admins group. Utilizing this privilege, I upload a vulnerable template and exploit the ECS1 vulnerability to obtain an Administrator certificate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTB Authority</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/htb-authority/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:33:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/htb-authority/</guid>
      <description>Authority is a medium Windows AD box. I discovered Ansible playbooks in a publicly accessible share, containing encrypted variables that, once cracked, provided credentials for the PWM configuration manager. With PWM in config mode, I could make changes without authentication, allowing the capture of clear text LDAP credentials for subsequent WinRM authentication. I also discovered ADCS and a vulnerable certificate template (ESC1). Although I successfully exploited the vulnerability, Kerberos limitations prevented authentication with the generated certificate. To bypass this I used pass-the-cert attack to gain access as Administrator.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
